deepcrawl.co.uk 2019-11-13

# Privacy Policy - DeepCrawl

This privacy policy governs the collection, storage and use of personal information collected by us, Written Byte Ltd (trading as DeepCrawl), via our website at [www.deepcrawl.com](https://www.deepcrawl.com/).

It provides you with details about the personal information we collect from you, how we use your personal information and your rights to control personal information we hold about you.

Please read this privacy policy carefully – by accessing or browsing this website, you confirm that you have read and understood this privacy policy in its entirety.

This privacy policy was last updated on 6th March 2018. Please check back  
regularly to keep informed of updates to this privacy policy.  

## Who We Are

Written Byte Ltd (trading as DeepCrawl) is a company registered in England and  
Wales (registration number 05936299), whose registered office is at:  
29 Throgmorton Street, London EC2N 2AT and we are the data controller of the  
personal information that we collect from you.

We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with applicable data protection and laws.

If you have any questions about how we collect, store and use personal  
information, or if you have any other privacy-related questions, please contact

Matt Jones who is our data protection officer by any of the following means:  
Matt Jones at mj@deepcrawl.com or by post at: 29 Throgmorton Street, London, EC2N 2AT, UK.  

## A Quick Word About Children

We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any unsupervised child  
under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you must not use this  
website unless you have the consent of, and are supervised by, a parent or  
guardian.  

## The Personal Information We Collect About You

When you access and browse this website (including when you submit personal  
information to us through data entry fields on the website), we may collect the following information from you:

● your name;  
● your age and sex;  
● your postal address;  
● your phone, fax and e-mail details;  
● credit card information for transactions; and  
● data about your computer hardware and software (such as IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses).  

## How We Store And Use Your Information

We collect, store and use your personal information listed above for the following purposes:  
● to make this website available to you;  
● to provide you with and maintain the quality of the DeepCrawl service;  
● to create a DeepCrawl account for you;  
● to complete the payment of any fees that you pay through the website for  
use of the DeepCrawl service; and  
● for any necessary communication between us and you regarding the  
DeepCrawl service.

Your personal information is processed in accordance with our legitimate interest in providing a service to you and monitoring and improving the use and  
satisfaction of our website.

Finally, we also collect anonymised details about visitors to our website for the purposes of aggregate statistics or reporting purposes. However, no single individual will be identifiable from the anonymised details we collect for these purposes.  

## How We Share Your Personal Information And Who We Share It With

We will disclose information under the following circumstances:

● Third-party service providers: When we share anonymous information  
with third-party service companies to facilitate or to provide certain  
services on our behalf. This will include companies that facilitate  
subscription billing for use of our services and website and companies that  
host our data (i.e. server providers). These companies are authorised to  
use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services  
to us.  
● Group companies: We will provide your personal information to our  
subsidiaries or affiliated companies for the purpose of processing personal  
information on our behalf to provide the website and services to you.  
These parties are required to process such information based on our instructions and in accordance with this privacy policy. They do not have  
any independent right to share this information.  
● Compliance with laws and legal proceedings: When we respond to court  
orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. When we believe in our sole discretion it is  
necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take  
actions against illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving  
potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our  
terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.  
● Merger or acquisition: When we need to transfer information about you if  
we are acquired by or merged with another company. If we are involved  
in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be  
notified afterwards via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of  
any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as  
any choices you may have regarding your personal information.  

## International Transfers

We will transfer personal information that we collect from you to third party  
service providers who host our data. They are located in the United States of  
America.

To ensure that third party service providers protect your personal  
information adequately and only use it in accordance with this privacy policy we have entered into the European Commission approved standard contractual  
arrangements with them.

We will transfer personal information that we collect from you to members of our group of companies located in countries that are outside of the European Economic Area (including to the United States of America) in connection with the above purposes.

To ensure that your personal information is adequately  
protected and only used in accordance with this privacy policy we have entered  
into the European Commission approved standard contractual arrangements  
with them.

Please be aware that countries which are outside the European Economic Area  
may not offer the same level of data protection as the United Kingdom, although our collection, storage and use of your personal data will continue to be governed by this privacy policy.

Further details on the steps we take to protect your personal information in  
these cases is available from us on request by emailing info@deepcrawl.com or writing to us at 29 Throgmorton Street, London EC2N 2AT.  

## Cookies

We use cookies on our website in accordance with our Cookie Policy. Please read more about how we use cookies and what information is collected using cookies [in our cookie policy here.](https://www.deepcrawl.com/cookie-policy/)  

## Security

Whilst we take appropriate technical and organisational measures to safeguard  
the personal information that you provide to us, no transmission over the  
Internet can ever be guaranteed secure.

Consequently, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any  
personal information that you transfer over the Internet to us.  

## Data Retention

We will retain information (including personal information) relating to your  
subscription and the services we provide to you for as long as you subscribe to our services and for up to five years after that time.

We will retain information used for marketing purposes for up to two years  
unless you let us know that you would like to opt-out of such communications.

We will delete personal information after the retention periods set out above except where we need to keep any personal information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.  

## Your Rights

You have the following rights:

● The right to ask us to provide you with copies of personal information that  
we hold about you at any time;  
● The right to ask us to update and correct any out-of- date or incorrect  
personal information that we hold about you free of charge; and  
● The right to opt out of any marketing communications that we (or any  
third party to whom we have disclosed your personal information with  
your consent) send you.

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please write to us (either by post or by e-mail) at the at info@deepcrawl.com or write to us at 29 Throgmorton Street, London EC2N 2AT.

If you want us to stop using or to delete your personal information, you can contact us and tell us why. In certain circumstances we may not be able to stop using your personal information but, if that is the case, we'll let you know and tell you why. If you wish to do this, please write to us (either by post or by e-mail) at info@deepcrawl.com or write to us at 29 Throgmorton Street, London EC2N 2AT

This website contains [links to other websites](http://test.chris24.co.uk/) operated by third parties.

Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the personal information that we collect through this website and we cannot be responsible for personal  
information that third parties may collect, store and use through their website.

You should always read the privacy policy of each website you visit carefully.

In the EEA, you may also make a complaint to our supervisory body for data protection matters (namely the Information Commissioner's Office) or seek a remedy through local courts if you believe your rights have been breached.
